https://outdoorwithj.com/privacy-policy/

Pinterest-p
Your privacy is critically important to us.
It is Outdoor With J’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://outdoorwithj.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://outdoorwithj.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Outdoor With J collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Outdoor With J’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Outdoor With J’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Outdoor With J may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Outdoor With J also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://outdoorwithj.com blog posts. Outdoor With J only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Outdoor With J’s websites choose to interact with Outdoor With J in ways that require Outdoor With J to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Outdoor With J gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://outdoorwithj.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Advertisements
Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Outdoor With J and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Outdoor With J discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Outdoor With J’s behalf or to provide services available at Outdoor With J’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Outdoor With J’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Outdoor With J will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Outdoor With J discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Outdoor With J believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Outdoor With J, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://outdoorwithj.com and have supplied your email address, Outdoor With J may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Outdoor With J and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Outdoor With J takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
Outdoor With J may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Outdoor With J may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Outdoor With J does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Affiliate Disclosure
This site uses affiliate links and does earn a commission from certain links. This does not affect your purchases or the price you may pay.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Outdoor With J uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Outdoor With J uses cookies to help Outdoor With J identify and track visitors, their usage of https://outdoorwithj.com, and their website access preferences. Outdoor With J visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Outdoor With J’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Outdoor With J’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Outdoor With J’s use of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Outdoor With J may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Outdoor With J’s sole discretion. Outdoor With J encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Credit & Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.
LET'S BEFRIENDS
Facebook-f
Twitter
Pinterest-p
Amazon Associates Disclaimer
As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
Home
About
Blog
Contact
Earning Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Menu
Home
Review
This website uses cookies and analytics to ensure you get the best experience on our website. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are as essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
